Guide to the Freedom Socialist Party and Radical Women Newspaper and Pamphlet Collection TAM.653
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Serials by Title, 1937-2002
  - The Other Side Publisher: Union of Sexual Minorities City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - The Ozark Feminist City of publication: Fayetteville, AR, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Pan International Publisher: Forbundet AF 1948, National League for Homophiles in Denmark City of publication: Copenhagen, Denmark, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Pandora City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1972-1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Partisan Review Publisher: Partisan Review City of publication: New York, NY, 1938, 1940, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Pension Facts Publisher: Pension Rights Center City of publication: Washington, D.C., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - The People Publisher: Socialist Labor Party City of publication: Palo Alto, CA, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - PFLP Bulletin Publisher: Popular Front for the Liberation of Palestine International Relations Committee City of publication: Beirut, Lebanon, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pike Market Senior Center Newsletter, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Plexus Publisher: Plexus City of publication: Berkeley, CA, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Point of Production Publisher: Bread and Roses City of publication: Austin, TX, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Poverty Law Report Publisher: Southern Poverty Law Center City of publication: Montgomery, AL, 1976-1978, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - The Practicing Midwife Publisher: The Book Publishing Co. City of publication: Sommertown, TN, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Priorities Publisher: British Columbia New Democratic Party Women's Rights Committee City of publication: Vancouver, BC, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Proud Publisher: Associated Students Publication, Western Washington State City of publication: Bellingham, WA, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Public Eye Publisher: Repression Information Project City of publication: Washington, D.C., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Quash Publisher: Grand Jury Project, New York Women's Union City of publication: New York, NY, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Quest: A Feminist Quarterly Publisher: Quest: A Feminist Quarterly, Inc. City of publication: Washington, D.C., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Radical America Publisher: Alternative Education Project, Inc. City of publication: Somerville, MA, 1975-1976, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ramblings Publisher: King County Rape Relief City of publication: Renton, WA, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Reason Publisher: Reason Enterprises City of publication: Santa Barbara, CA, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Recobrando Publisher: El Centro de la Raza City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Red Dragon Publisher: NWPO City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Red Flag Publisher: Red Flag Union City of publication: Hollywood, CA, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Red Letter Publisher: Native American Committee, Inc City of publication: Chicago, IL, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Resist Publisher: Resist City of publication: Somerville, MA, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Review of International Affairs Publisher: Federation of Yugoslav Journalists City of publication: Belgrade, Serbia, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Revolution Publisher: Central Committee of the Revolutionary Communist Party, USA City of publication: Chicago, IL, 1976, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Revolutionary Worker Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA City of publication: New York, NY, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Rising River Publisher: Boston University Women's Center City of publication: Boston, MA, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Rouge Publisher: Societe de presse nouvelle, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Rural America Publisher: Rural America, Inc. City of publication: Washington, D.C., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Samasamajist Publisher: Lanka Samasamaja Party Section of the Fourth International City of publication: Colombo, Sri Lanka, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - The San Francisco Journal Publisher: The San Francisco Journal City of publication: San Francisco, CA, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - SANEnews Publisher: Community Health Center, Inc City of publication: Middletown, CT, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Sanity Now! City of publication: La Puente, CA, 1977, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Sappho Publisher: Sappho Publications Ltd. City of publication: London, UK, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - The Scanner and King County Labor News Publisher: King County Labor Council of Washington, AFL-CIO City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Science and Society Publisher: Science and Society, Inc. City of publication: New York, NY, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Science for the People Publisher: Science Resource Center, Inc. City of publication: Cambridge, MA, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Seattle Gay News Publisher: Gay Community Center City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 34-36, Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Seattle Semi Publisher: Seattle Semi, Teamster Rank and File City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - The Seattle Sun Publisher: Seattle Information Project City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1974-1980 (Box 8, Folder 3-6)
  - Seattle Voice Publisher: SeattleVOICE, Inc. City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Seattle Women Act for Peace Newsletter Publisher: Seattle Women Act for Peace City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Seattle Worker Publisher: Central Branch of U.S. Marxist-Leninists, Seattle Branch City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - The Second Wave Publisher: The Second Wave City of publication: Cambridge, MA, 1977, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Seven Days Publisher: Institute for New Communications, Inc. City of publication: New York, NY, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Seven Eagles Publisher: Leonard Peltier Defense Committee, Canada City of publication: Vancouver, BC, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Shelterforce Publisher: Shelterforce Collective and National Lawyers Guild City of publication: East Orange, NJ, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Signs: Journal of Women in Culture and Society Publisher: University of Chicago Press City of publication: Chicago, IL, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Sin Fronteras Publisher: Sin Fronteras Publications, Inc. City of publication: Los Angeles, CA, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Sister: West Coast Feminist Newspaper Publisher: The Women's Center City of publication: Venice, CA, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - SisterSource: A Midwest Feminist Newspaper Publisher: SisterSource, Inc. City of publication: Chicago, IL, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Social Policy Publisher: International Arts and Sciences Press, Inc. City of publication: White Plains, NY, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Socialist Appeal Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, Fourth International City of publication: London, UK, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Socialist Fight Publisher: Socialist Fight City of publication: Australia, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Socialist Forum Publisher: Socialist Committee of Correspondence City of publication: New York, NY, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Socialist Republic Publisher: Peoples' Democracy City of publication: Dublin, Ireland, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Socialist Voice Publisher: Socialist Voice Publishing City of publication: Toronto, ON, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Socialist Woman Publisher: International Marxist Group City of publication: London, UK, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Socialist Woman Publisher: Socialist Woman Groups City of publication: London, UK, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Socialist Worker Publisher: International Socialist Organization City of publication: Cleveland, OH, 1977, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Society Publisher: Rutgers City of publication: New Brunswick, NJ, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Sojourner Publisher: Sojourner Feminist Institute City of publication: Cambridge, MA, 1981, 1993-2002 (Box 8, Folder 28, Box 10, Folder 1-9, Box 9)
  - South Asia Marxist Review Publisher: South Asia Marxist Review City of publication: London, UK, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - South Seattle Women's Network Publisher: Rainier Vista Community Health Clinic City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Southeast Asia Chronicle Publisher: Southeast Asia Resource Center City of publication: Berkeley, CA, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Southern Africa Publisher: Southern Africa City of publication: New York, NY, 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
  - Southern Agitator Publisher: Southern Agitator City of publication: New Orleans, LA, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Spare Rib Publisher: Spare Rib City of publication: London, UK, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Spartacist-West Publisher: Bay Area Spartacist League City of publication: Berkeley, CA, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Spirit of the People Publisher: Native American Solidarity Committee City of publication: St. Paul, MN, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Spokane Natural Publisher: Mandala Printshop City of publication: Spokane, WA, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - The Starry Plough Publisher: Irish Republican Socialist Party, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - State and Mind Publisher: Radical Therapist, Inc City of publication: Somerville, MA, 1977, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Steel Labor City of publication: Pittsburgh, PA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Student Socialist Publisher: Socialist Student Alliance City of publication: New York, NY, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - SWP Discussion Bulletin Publisher: Socialist Workers Party City of publication: New York, NY, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Synapse Publisher: Armistice City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Tacoma Indian News Publisher: Tacoma Indian News City of publication: Tacoma, WA, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Through the Looking Glass Publisher: Through the Looking Glass City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - TightWire Publisher: Tightwire Publications City of publication: Kingston, ON, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Torch Publisher: Revolutionary Socialist League City of publication: New York, NY, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Transnational Perspectives Publisher: Transnational Perspectives City of publication: Geneva, Switzerland, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Trotskyism Today Publisher: Workers Socialist League City of publication: London, UK, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Truth Publisher: Trotskyist Organization of the USA City of publication: Detroit, MI, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - United Workers Organizer Publisher: United Workers Union City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Update Publisher: The Body Politic Free the Press Fund City of publication: Toronto, ON, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Viet-Report Publisher: Viet-Report, Inc. City of publication: New York, NY, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Voice Publisher: West Coast Regional Joint Board Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union City of publication: Los Angeles, CA, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Washington Monthly Publisher: Washington Monthly City of publication: Washington, D.C., 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Washington Report on the Hemisphere Publisher: Council on Hemispheric Affairs City of publication: Washington, D.C., 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - The Washington Spectator and Between the Lines Publisher: The Washington Spectator, Inc. City of publication: Washington, D.C., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Washington Teamster Publisher: Joint Council No. 28 City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - The Weekly People Publisher: Socialist Labor Party City of publication: Palo Alto, CA, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Weekly Publication of the Moslem Students Society-Britain Publisher: Moslem Students Society-Britain City of publication: London, UK, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - What She Wants Publisher: What She Wants City of publication: Cleveland, OH, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - WIN Publisher: WIN Publishing Empire, War Resisters League City of publication: New York, NY, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Women and Politics Publisher: Haworth Press, Inc. City of publication: Binghamton, NY, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Women and Revolution Publisher: Women's Commission of the Spartacist League City of publication: New York, NY, 1973, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Women and Struggle in Iran Publisher: Women's Commission of the Iranian Students Association in the U.S. City of publication: Chicago, IL, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - The Workers Advocate Publisher: Central Organization of U.S. Marxist-Leninists City of publication: Chicago IL, 1976, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Workers' Democracy Publisher: Workers' Democracy City of publication: St Louis, MO, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Workers International News Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, Fourth International City of publication: London, UK, 1943-1945 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Workers' Power Publisher: International Socialist Publishing Company City of publication: Highland Park, MI, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Workers Press Publisher: Central Committee of the Socialist Labour League City of publication: London, UK, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Workers Struggle Publisher: Revolutionary Workers League City of publication: Detroit, MI, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Workers' Unity Publisher: South African Congress of Trade Unions, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Workers Vanguard Publisher: Spartacist League of the U.S. City of publication: New York, NY, 1973, 1977, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Workers Viewpoint Publisher: Communist Workers Party City of publication: New York, NY, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Workers World Publisher: World View Publishers, Inc. City of publication: New York, NY, 1975, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Workforce Publisher: Vocations for Social Change City of publication: Canyon, CA, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - World Magazine City of publication: Delano, CA, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - World Outlook Publisher: Pierre Frank City of publication: Paris, France, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - World Revolution Publisher: International Communist Current City of publication: London, UK, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - The Young Socialist Publisher: Young Socialist Alliance City of publication: New York, NY, 1963, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Young Socialist Discussion Bulletin Publisher: Young Socialist Alliance City of publication: New York, NY, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Young Spartacus Publisher: Spartacus Youth League City of publication: New York, NY, 1976, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Your Life!; Su Vida Publisher: Youth Workers of the NYC Unemployed and Welfare Council Summer Youth Program City of publication: New York, NY, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Yvonne Wanrow News Publisher: Indian Legal Defense Committee City of publication: Inchelium, WA, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Series II: Pamphlets by Title, 1943-1979
  This series includes a small number of pamphlets published by a variety of organizations, including the Liberation Support Movement Information Center, Pathfinder Press (Socialist Workers Party), Peoples Democracy and the Communist Party. Subjects addressed include socialism, Trotskyism and revolutionary organizing, civil rights, gay liberation, and others. International issues in countries including Angola, Ireland and South Africa are included. There are also a small number of directories and U.S. government publications.
  - Alternative America: A Directory of 5000 Alternative Lifestyle Groups and Organizations Publisher: Alternative America City of publication: Cambridge, MA, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Anatomy of Apartheid in Southern Africa by Franz J.T. Lee Publisher: Alexander Defense Committee City of publication: New York, NY, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Anglola MPLA: Seta Likambuila Publisher: Liberation Support Movement Information Center City of publication: Richmond, BC, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Angola MPLA: Paulo Jorge Publisher: Liberation Support Movement Information Center City of publication: Richmond, BC, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Angola MPLA: Spartacus Monimambu Publisher: Liberation Support Movement Information Center City of publication: Richmond, BC, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Background Facts on Women Workers in the United States Publisher: Women's Bureau, Wage and Labor Standards Administration, U.S. Department of Labor City of publication: Washington, D.C., 1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Black Hills Alliance Publisher: The Black Hills Alliance City of publication: Rapid City, SD, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bulletin List (1939-1959) Publisher: Socialist Workers Party City of publication: New York, NY (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - C.A.S.A General Brotherhood of Workers, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The Civil Rights Act of 1964 Publisher: U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare City of publication: Washington, D.C. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Constitution of the Socialist Workers Party Publisher: Socialist Workers Party, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The Devlopment of the PRI and the Mexican Left by Alfonso Rios Publisher: Imprecor, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Dividing Line of the 80's: Take a Stand against the Klan Publisher: John Brown Anti-Klan Committee City of publication: New York, NY, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Draft Program and Constitution: Communist Party U.S.A. Publisher: UNITE! City of publication: Chicago, IL, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Fight Against Racism in our Schools by Luis Fuentes Publisher: Pathfinder Press, Inc. City of publication: New York, NY, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - For Fusion with the Socialist Workers Party Publisher: Third National Conference of the Revolutionary Marxist Committee, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Forced Treatment = Torture Publisher: Network Against Psychiatric Assault City of publication: San Francisco, CA, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Gay Liberation Publisher: The Red Butterfly City of publication: New York, NY, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Gay Liberation and Socialism: Documents from the Discussion on Gay Liberation Inside the Socialist Workers Party (1970-1973) by David Thorstad City of publication: New York, NY, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - H-Block Struggle: Irish Revolution on the March Publisher: Peoples Democracy City of publication: Belfast, Northern Ireland, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Internment '71 H-Block '81: The Same Struggle Publisher: Peoples Democracy City of publication: Belfast, Northern Ireland, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Ireland for Sale: The Roots of the Economic Crisis Publisher: Peoples Democracy City of publication: Belfast, Northern Ireland, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Issues Facing the Labor Movement in the 1970's edited by Paul Davidson Publisher: Pathfinder Press, Inc. City of publication: New York, NY, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - National Institute of Mental Health Task Force on Homosexuality: Final Report and Background Papers Publisher: National Institute of Mental Health City of publication: Rockville, MD, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Notes on a Strategy for North American Revolutionaries by Don Barnett Publisher: Liberation Support Movement Information Center City of publication: Richmond, BC, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - A People Undefeated: Ten Years of Struggle in the North of Ireland by John McAnulty Publisher: Peoples Democracy City of publication: Belfast, Northern Ireland, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Portugal: Anti-Fascism or Anti-Capitalism Publisher: Root and Branch City of publication: Somerville, MA, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Resistance Against Fascist Enslavement in South Africa Publisher: New Century Publishers City of publication: New York, NY, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The Revolution (Reprint) Publisher: KNOW, Inc City of publication: New York, NY, 1868 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Revolutionary Analysis, Strategy and Tactics Today Publisher: Merit Pamplet City of publication: New York, NY, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The Road to Peace by James P. Cannon Publisher: Pioneer Publishers, Socialist Workers Party City of publication: New York, NY, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Roots of the Mideast War Publisher: International Socialist Review Publishing Association City of publication: New York, NY, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The Russian Revolution by James P. Cannon Publisher: Socialist Workers Party City of publication: New York, NY, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Seattle City Government: A Handbook for Citizens Publisher: League of Women Voters of Seattle City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Socialist Election Policy in 1958 by James P. Cannon Publisher: Pioneer Publishers, Socialist Workers Party City of publication: New York, NY, circa 1958 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Socialist Labor Party speaks on Vital Issues of 1976 Publisher: Socialist Labor Party City of publication: Palo Alto, CA, circa 1976 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Staff Association Union Contract 1976-1977 Publisher: Pierce County Library City of publication: Tacoma, WA (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Stalin's Life by Dyson Carter Publisher: Contemporary Publishers City of publication: Winnipeg, MB, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - The Struggle Against the Tito Fascists - Agents of Imperialism Publisher: National Education Department of the Communist Party City of publication: New York, NY, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Teheran and America by Earl Browder Publisher: Workers Library Publishers City of publication: New York, NY, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Toward a Scientific Analysis of the Gay Question Publisher: Los Angeles Research Group City of publication: Los Angeles, CA, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Toward an International Strategy by Don Barnett Publisher: Liberation Support Movement Information Center City of publication: Richmond, BC, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Toward the Divorce of Psychiatry and Law by Lee Coleman, M.D. Publisher: Virginia Law Weekly, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Two Articles on Trotskyism Publisher: UNITE!, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Washington Black Business Directory Publisher: Washington Black Business Newspaper City of publication: Seattle, WA, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - What Have Women Done? Publisher: San Francisco Women's History Group, United Front Press City of publication: San Francisco, CA, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - What Socialists Stand For by Stephanie Coontz Publisher: Pathfinder Press, Inc. City of publication: New York, NY, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - What's Happening in the Phillipines? by Samuel P. Bayani Publisher: Far East Reporter City of publication: New York, NY, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - What's to be Done! Publisher: Communard Publishers City of publication: Houston, TX, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - With Freedom in their Eyes: A Photo-Essay of Angola Publisher: Peoples Press City of publication: San Francisco, CA, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Series III: Subject Files, 1937-1982
  This series contains subject files, which are comprised of newspapers and pamphlets that were arranged topically by the Freedom Socialist Party and Radical Women. Newspaper titles, and even individual issues, included in Series I may also be found in this series. The subjects included in Series III are representative of the collection as a whole, with additional emphasis on international issues.
  - Black Struggle, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Gay Liberation, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Gay Rights, 1973-1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Hungary, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - International Marxist Group, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - International Socialist, 1974, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Iran Liberation (Mojahaden), 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Korea, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Labor, 1943, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 20)